Inventory of the W. W. Morrison Papers, 1804-1977
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Maps And Plats, 1848-1972 (Box 26 (clamshell))
  - Trails and Territories: full routes and areas
    - Lander's Cutoff (Fort Kearney, South Pass & Honey Lake Wagon Road), photocopy of 1857-1858 survey map
    - Mormon Trail, published, 1947
    - Old Oregon Territory 1848, showing various trails, published, no date, 2 copies
    - Oregon Trail, published, 1938, 1948, 3 items
    - Pony Express Route, published, 1960, 3 items
    - Trails Of The Old West, by W.H. Jackson, published, no date
  - States
    - Kansas: Oregon Trail through Kansas, hand-drawn by Paul Henderson, 1954, 3 sheets
    - Colorado
      - Colorado-Wyoming highway map, published, 1970
      - Denver street map, published, no date
      - Weld County, published, 1948
    - Wyoming: Oregon Trail plus other emigrant and stage roads, drawn on contour and township maps by L.C. Bishop, 1952-1959
      - Torrington area, 2 copies
      - Grattan Massacre area, 2 copies
      - Fort Laramie and Fort Fetterman areas
      - Fort Casper, Independence Rock, South Pass areas
      - Parting Of The Ways
      - Fort Bridger area
      - Lander Cutoff
      - Fort Russell area, 2 copies
      - Fort Sanders area
- Maps And Plats, 1940-1972 (Box 27 (clamshell))
  - States
    - Wyoming
      - Oregon Trail plus other emigrant and stage roads, drawn on USGS quadrangle maps by L.C. Bishop or unidentified, 1952-1953, 1 set of 15 sheets, 1 set of 23 sheets, 1 set of 30 sheets
      - Emigrant trails in Eastern Wyoming, hand-drawn by Helen Henderson or unidentified, 1970 & no date, 2 items
      - Cheyenne street map, no date
      - South Pass City plat, drawn by Paul Henderson, 1955
      - Highway maps, published, 1940, 1950, 1972, 3 items
      - Township 33N Range 80W, official resurvey, 1935
      - USGS quadrangles, arranged alphabetically, some with trails marked, 1950-1966, 35 sheets, also USGS quadrangle index
    - South Dakota
      - South Dakota-North Dakota highway map, 1963
      - Crazy Horse Canyon, Rosebud Sioux Reservation, tourist publication, no date, 4 copies
    - Montana: Historic Montana Trails, tourist publication, 1954, 4 copies
- Maps And Plats, 1853-1968 (Box 28 (clamshell))
  - States
    - Mitchell's New Map of Texas, Oregon and California, by S.A. Mitchell, 1925 reprint of 1846 publication
    - California
      - Bloody Point Sector, survey by Devere Helfrich, 1948
      - Nevada County, published, no date
      - Sacramento, picture map and rainfall & temperature chart 1877-1956, published, no dates, 2 items
    - Oregon
      - Oregon Trail from Eastern Oregon to the Columbia, hand-marked on county maps, no author, no date, 7 sheets
      - Umatilla County, published, no date
    - Washington
      - Pattison Lake-Chambers Prairie area, photocopies and blueprints, 1853, 1863, 1915 and undated surveys, 4 items
      - Lewis County (location of Pattisons' first home), 1935 survey
      - Walla Walla County, published, no date
    - Miscellaneous
      - Cambria County, Pennsylvania, published, no date
      - Hawaii, highway map, 1968
      - Eastern United States, highway map, 1969
- Newspapers, 1955-1975 (Box 28 (clamshell))
  - John Hunton's diary 1877-1879, as published in the Lingle, Wyoming Guide-Review, incomplete, 1955-1956, scrapbook of clippings
  - "Old Fort Report", life at Fort D.A. Russell 1868-1904, column by Martha Fleishman and Carol Joy Justice in unidentified Cheyenne paper, 1974-1975, 1 file
- Newspapers, 1947-1973 (Box 29)
  - Wyoming State Tribune and other Wyoming, Nebraska, Oregon, Washington, and Ohio newspapers, containing "in Old Wyoming" columns and other articles by W.W. Morrison or based on material supplied by him, regarding pioneer graves, Rock Creek Church, Indian captivities, etc., 59 items
- Newspapers And Newspaper Clippings, 1885-1978 (Box 30)
  - Cheyenne Daily Sun, 1885 issue (poor condition), and reproduction of 1890 issue
  - Denver Post magazine sections with articles on Chief Joseph, western bad men, White House history, 1955-1964, 3 items
  - Oregon City Enterprise, centennial issue, 1948
  - Ouray County (Colorado) Plain Dealer, centennial supplement with county history, 1976
  - The Pony Express, specialty paper, Jan. 1957-Feb. 1958, 9 items
  - Early History of Saratoga and Vicinity, single issue paper, 1976
  - Pages from Denver Post regarding death of Baby Doe Tabor, 1935; also 2 copies of Colorado Prospector and page of unidentified Cheyenne paper regarding Baby Doe, Molly Brown, no dates & 1976
  - Page from St. Louis Dispatch, "Indians In The United States Today", 1901
  - Page from Wyoming Eagle regarding Morse Code Club with photo including Morrison, 1976
  - Clippings of "In Old Wyoming" columns and other items of Wyoming and Western history or of personal interest, 1914-1978, 146 scrapbook pages + 2 files